const newTestament = [
  // 10-point questions (easy)
  {
    question: "Name the odd one out",
    options: ["Thomas", "Levi", "Simon the zealot", "Luke"],
    correctOption: 3,
    points: 5,
  },
  {
    question: "What angel of God appeared to Mary, the mother of Jesus?",
    options: ["Angel Uriel", "Angel Michael", "Angel Gabriel", "Angel Raphael"],
    correctOption: 2,
    points: 5,
  },
  {
    question: "in the transfiguration, Jesus was alongside two men namely:",
    options: [
      "Jeremiah and Elijah",
      "Elisha and Moses",
      "Moses and Abraham",
      "Moses and Elijah",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
    points: 5,
  },
  {
    question:
      "According to John's account of ressurrection, what disciple did he outrun on the way to the tomb?",
    options: [
      "James the less",
      "Simon Peter",
      "James, son of Zeebedee",
      "Andrew",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
    points: 5,
  },
  {
    question:
      "'Faith without good works is dead'. who can this saying be attributed to?",
    options: ["St. Paul", "St. James", "St. John", "St. Luke"],
    correctOption: 1,
    points: 5,
  },

  // 10-point questions (medium)
  {
    question:
      "'I am the Way, the Truth and the Life...', choose the corresponding verse",
    options: ["John 3:34", "Matthew 21:10", "John 9:8", "John 14:6"],
    correctOption: 3,
    points: 10,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What passage in the scripture did Jesus open and read aloud in the synagogue?",
    options: ["Isaiah ...", "Jeremiah ...", "1st Kings ...", "Psalm..."],
    correctOption: 0,
    points: 10,
  },
  {
    question:
      "The passion of our Lord Jesus Christ according to Luke, Christ was the reason Pilate and __ reconciled after he was sent for further humiliation",
    options: ["Caiaphas", "Herod", "Annas", "The Sanhedrin"],
    correctOption: 1,
    points: 10,
  },
  {
    question:
      "One of these disciple was asked by God in a vision to help Saul regain his eyesight",
    options: ["Peter", "Ananias", "Nicodemus", "Stephen"],
    correctOption: 1,
    points: 15,
  },
  {
    question: "One of these are Mary's parents",
    options: [
      "Simon and Anna",
      "Jeremiah and Hannah",
      "Anne and Cleopas",
      "Ann and Joachim",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
    points: 15,
  },
  {
    question:
      "According to the Gospels, what is the unique literary genre Jesus employs to teach his message?",
    options: [
      "Idioms",
      "Proverbial sayings",
      "Parables",
      "Melodrama/Fan fiction",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
    points: 15,
  },
  {
    question: "In what City was Jesus born?",
    options: ["Nazareth", "Egypt", "Canaan", "Bethlehem"],
    correctOption: 3,
    points: 15,
  },
  {
    question: "How many of the healed ten(10) lepers returned to thank Jesus?",
    options: ["0", "1", "9", "5"],
    correctOption: 1,
    points: 15,
  },

  // 20-point questions (hard)
  {
    question: "What is the shortest verse in the bible?",
    options: ["Acts 2:12", "John 11:35", "1 Peter 1:3", "John 3:16"],
    correctOption: 1,
    points: 20,
  },
  {
    question:
      "The new testament was mostly originally written in what language?",
    options: ["Hebrew", "Latin", "Greek", "None of the above"],
    correctOption: 2,
    points: 20,
  },
  {
    question: "Who helped a Eunuch to understand a portion of the bible?",
    options: ["Matthias", "Silas", "Barnabas", "Phillip"],
    correctOption: 3,
    points: 30,
  },
];

export default newTestament;
